[{"question":" If you want to import just the Component from the React library, what syntax do you use?","options":[{"text":"`import React.Component from 'react'`","correct":false},{"text":"`import [ Component ] from 'react'`","correct":false},{"text":"`import Component from 'react'`","correct":false},{"text":"`import { Component } from 'react'`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" If a function component should always render the same way given the same props, what is a simple performance optimization available for it?","options":[{"text":"Wrap it in the `React.memo` higher-order component.","correct":true},{"text":"Implement the `useReducer` Hook.","correct":false},{"text":"Implement the `useMemo` Hook.","correct":false},{"text":"Implement the `shouldComponentUpdate` lifecycle method.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How do you fix the syntax error that results from running this code?","options":[{"text":"Wrap the object in parentheses.","correct":true},{"text":"Call the function from another file.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a return statement before the first curly brace.","correct":false},{"text":"Replace the object with an array.","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst person =(firstName, lastName) =>\n{\n  first: firstName,\n  last: lastName\n}\nconsole.log(person(\"Jill\", \"Wilson\"))\n```"},{"question":" If you see the following import in a file, what is being used for state management in the component?","options":[{"text":"React Hooks","correct":true},{"text":"stateful components","correct":false},{"text":"math","correct":false},{"text":"class components","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Using object literal enhancement, you can put values back into an object. When you log person to the console, what is the output?","options":[{"text":"`{{name: \"Rachel\", age: 31}}`","correct":false},{"text":"`{name: \"Rachel\", age: 31}`","correct":true},{"text":"`{person: \"Rachel\", person: 31}}`","correct":false},{"text":"`{person: {name: \"Rachel\", age: 31}}`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst name = 'Rachel';\nconst age = 31;\nconst person = { name, age };\nconsole.log(person);\n```"},{"question":" What is the testing library most often associated with React?","options":[{"text":"Mocha","correct":false},{"text":"Chai","correct":false},{"text":"Sinon","correct":false},{"text":"Jest","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" To get the first item from the array (\"cooking\") using array destructuring, how do you adjust this line?","options":[{"text":"`const first = [\"cooking\", \"art\", \"history\"]`","correct":false},{"text":"`const [] = [\"cooking\", \"art\", \"history\"]`","correct":false},{"text":"`const [, first][\"cooking\", \"art\", \"history\"]`","correct":false},{"text":"`const [first] = [\"cooking\", \"art\", \"history\"]`","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst topics = ['cooking', 'art', 'history'];\n```"},{"question":" How do you handle passing through the component tree without having to pass props down manually at every level?","options":[{"text":"React Send","correct":false},{"text":"React Pinpoint","correct":false},{"text":"React Router","correct":false},{"text":"React Context","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What should the console read when the following code is run?","options":[{"text":"Horse","correct":false},{"text":"Cat","correct":true},{"text":"Mouse","correct":false},{"text":"undefined","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst [, , animal] = ['Horse', 'Mouse', 'Cat'];\nconsole.log(animal);\n```"},{"question":" What is the name of the tool used to take JSX and turn it into createElement calls?","options":[{"text":"JSX Editor","correct":false},{"text":"ReactDOM","correct":false},{"text":"Browser Buddy","correct":false},{"text":"Babel","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Why might you use useReducer over useState in a React component?","options":[{"text":"when you want to replace Redux","correct":false},{"text":"when you need to manage more complex state in an app","correct":true},{"text":"when you want to improve performance","correct":false},{"text":"when you want to break your production app","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which props from the props object is available to the component with the following syntax?","options":[{"text":"any that have not changed","correct":false},{"text":"all of them","correct":true},{"text":"child props","correct":false},{"text":"any that have changed","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\n<Message {...props} />\n```"},{"question":" Consider the following code from React Router. What do you call :id in the path prop?","options":[{"text":"This is a route modal","correct":false},{"text":"This is a route parameter","correct":true},{"text":"This is a route splitter","correct":false},{"text":"This is a route link","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\n<Route path=\"/:id\" />\n```"},{"question":" If you created a component called Dish and rendered it to the DOM, what type of element would be rendered?","options":[{"text":"`div`","correct":false},{"text":"section","correct":false},{"text":"component","correct":false},{"text":"`h1`","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nfunction Dish() {\n  return <h1>Mac and Cheese</h1>;\n}\nReactDOM.render(<Dish />, document.getElementById('root'));\n```"},{"question":" What does this React element look like given the following function? (Alternative: Given the following code, what does this React element look like?)","options":[{"text":"`<h1 props={null}>What's happening?</h1>`","correct":false},{"text":"`<h1>What's happening?</h1>`","correct":true},{"text":"`<h1 id=\"component\">What's happening?</h1>`","correct":false},{"text":"`<h1 id=\"element\">What's happening?</h1>`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nReact.createElement('h1', null, \"What's happening?\");\n```"},{"question":" What property do you need to add to the Suspense component in order to display a spinner or loading state?","options":[{"text":"lazy","correct":false},{"text":"loading","correct":false},{"text":"fallback","correct":true},{"text":"spinner","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nfunction MyComponent() {\n  return (\n    <Suspense>\n      <div>\n        <Message />\n      </div>\n    </Suspense>\n  );\n}\n```"},{"question":" What do you call the message wrapped in curly braces below?","options":[{"text":"a JS function","correct":false},{"text":"a JS element","correct":false},{"text":"a JS expression","correct":true},{"text":"a JSX wrapper","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst message = 'Hi there';\nconst element = <p>{message}</p>;\n```"},{"question":" What can you use to handle code splitting?","options":[{"text":"`React.memo`","correct":false},{"text":"`React.split`","correct":false},{"text":"`React.lazy`","correct":true},{"text":"`React.fallback`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When do you use `useLayoutEffect`?","options":[{"text":"to optimize for all devices","correct":false},{"text":"to complete the update","correct":false},{"text":"to change the layout of the screen","correct":false},{"text":"when you need the browser to paint before the effect runs","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the difference between the click behaviors of these two buttons (assuming that this.handleClick is bound correctly)?","options":[{"text":"Button A will not have access to the event object on click of the button.","correct":false},{"text":"Button B will not fire the handler this.handleClick successfully.","correct":false},{"text":"Button A will not fire the handler this.handleClick successfully.","correct":false},{"text":"There is no difference.","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nA. <button onClick={this.handleClick}>Click Me</button>\nB. <button onClick={event => this.handleClick(event)}>Click Me</button>\n```"},{"question":" How do you destructure the properties that are sent to the Dish component?","options":[{"text":"`function Dish([name, cookingTime]) { return <h1>{name} {cookingTime}</h1>; }`","correct":false},{"text":"`function Dish({name, cookingTime}) { return <h1>{name} {cookingTime}</h1>; }`","correct":true},{"text":"`function Dish(props) { return <h1>{name} {cookingTime}</h1>; }`","correct":false},{"text":"`function Dish(...props) { return <h1>{name} {cookingTime}</h1>; }`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nfunction Dish(props) {\n  return (\n    <h1>\n      {props.name} {props.cookingTime}\n    </h1>\n  );\n}\n```"},{"question":" When might you use `React.PureComponent`?","options":[{"text":"when you do not want your component to have props","correct":false},{"text":"when you have sibling components that need to be compared","correct":false},{"text":"when you want a default implementation of `shouldComponentUpdate()`","correct":true},{"text":"when you do not want your component to have state","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Why is it important to avoid copying the values of props into a component's state where possible?","options":[{"text":"because you should never mutate state","correct":false},{"text":"because `getDerivedStateFromProps()` is an unsafe method to use","correct":false},{"text":"because you want to allow a component to update in response to changes in the props","correct":true},{"text":"because you want to allow data to flow back up to the parent","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the children prop?","options":[{"text":"a property that adds child components to state","correct":false},{"text":"a property that lets you pass components as data to other components","correct":true},{"text":"a property that lets you set an array as a property","correct":false},{"text":"a property that lets you pass data to child elements","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which attribute do you use to replace innerHTML in the browser DOM?","options":[{"text":"injectHTML","correct":false},{"text":"dangerouslySetInnerHTML","correct":true},{"text":"weirdSetInnerHTML","correct":false},{"text":"strangeHTML","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which of these terms commonly describe React applications?","options":[{"text":"declarative","correct":true},{"text":"integrated","correct":false},{"text":"closed","correct":false},{"text":"imperative","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When using webpack, why would you need to use a loader?","options":[{"text":"to put together physical file folders","correct":false},{"text":"to preprocess files","correct":true},{"text":"to load external data","correct":false},{"text":"to load the website into everyone's phone","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" A representation of a user interface that is kept in memory and is synced with the \"real\" DOM is called what?","options":[{"text":"virtual DOM","correct":true},{"text":"DOM","correct":false},{"text":"virtual elements","correct":false},{"text":"shadow DOM","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have written the following code but nothing is rendering. How do you fix this problem?","options":[{"text":"Add a render function.","correct":false},{"text":"Change the curly braces to parentheses or add a return statement before the `h1` tag.","correct":true},{"text":"Move the `h1` to another component.","correct":false},{"text":"Surround the `h1` in a `div`.","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst Heading = () => {\n  <h1>Hello!</h1>;\n};\n```"},{"question":". To create a constant in JavaScript, which keyword do you use?","options":[{"text":"const","correct":true},{"text":"let","correct":false},{"text":"constant","correct":false},{"text":"var","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What do you call a React component that catches JavaScript errors anywhere in the child component tree?","options":[{"text":"error bosses","correct":false},{"text":"error catchers","correct":false},{"text":"error helpers","correct":false},{"text":"error boundaries","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In which lifecycle method do you make requests for data in a class component?","options":[{"text":"constructor","correct":false},{"text":"componentDidMount","correct":true},{"text":"componentWillReceiveProps","correct":false},{"text":"componentWillMount","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". React components are composed to create a user interface. How are components composed?","options":[{"text":"by putting them in the same file","correct":false},{"text":"by nesting components","correct":true},{"text":"with webpack","correct":false},{"text":"with code splitting","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". All React components must act like `**\\_\\_**` with respect to their props.","options":[{"text":"monads","correct":false},{"text":"pure functions","correct":true},{"text":"recursive functions","correct":false},{"text":"higher-order functions","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why might you use a ref?","options":[{"text":"to directly access the DOM node","correct":true},{"text":"to refer to another JS file","correct":false},{"text":"to call a function","correct":false},{"text":"to bind the function","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is `[e.target.id]` called in the following code snippet?","options":[{"text":"a computed property name","correct":false},{"text":"a set value","correct":false},{"text":"a dynamic key","correct":true},{"text":"a JSX code string","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nhandleChange(e) {\n  this.setState({ [e.target.id]: e.target.value })\n}\n```"},{"question":". What is the name of this component?","options":[{"text":"Clock","correct":true},{"text":"It does not have a name prop.","correct":false},{"text":"React.Component","correct":false},{"text":"Component","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nclass Clock extends React.Component {\n  render() {\n    return <h1>Look at the time: {time}</h1>;\n  }\n}\n```"},{"question":". What is sent to an `Array.map()` function?","options":[{"text":"a callback function that is called once for each element in the array","correct":true},{"text":"the name of another array to iterate over","correct":false},{"text":"the number of times you want to call the function","correct":false},{"text":"a string describing what the function should do","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why is it a good idea to pass a function to `setState` instead of an object?","options":[{"text":"It provides better encapsulation.","correct":false},{"text":"It makes sure that the object is not mutated.","correct":false},{"text":"It automatically updates a component.","correct":false},{"text":"`setState` is asynchronous and might result in out of sync values.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What package contains the render() function that renders a React element tree to the DOM?","options":[{"text":"`React`","correct":false},{"text":"`ReactDOM`","correct":true},{"text":"`Render`","correct":false},{"text":"`DOM`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How do you set a default value for an uncontrolled form field?","options":[{"text":"Use the `value` property.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the `defaultValue` property.","correct":true},{"text":"Use the `default` property.","correct":false},{"text":"It assigns one automatically.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What do you need to change about this code to get it to run?","options":[{"text":"Add quotes around the return value","correct":false},{"text":"Remove `this`","correct":false},{"text":"Remove the render method","correct":false},{"text":"Capitalize `clock`","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```js\nclass clock extends React.Component {\n  render() {\n    return <h1>Look at the time: {this.props.time}</h1>;\n  }\n}\n```"},{"question":". Which Hook could be used to update the document's title?","options":[{"text":"`useEffect(function updateTitle() { document.title = name + ' ' + lastname; });`","correct":true},{"text":"`useEffect(() => { title = name + ' ' + lastname; });`","correct":false},{"text":"`useEffect(function updateTitle() { name + ' ' + lastname; });`","correct":false},{"text":"`useEffect(function updateTitle() { title = name + ' ' + lastname; });`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What can you use to wrap Component imports in order to load them lazily?","options":[{"text":"`React.fallback`","correct":false},{"text":"`React.split`","correct":false},{"text":"`React.lazy`","correct":true},{"text":"`React.memo`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How do you invoke setDone only when component mounts, using hooks?","options":[{"text":"`useEffect(() => { setDone(true); });`","correct":false},{"text":"`useEffect(() => { setDone(true); }, []);`","correct":true},{"text":"`useEffect(() => { setDone(true); }, [setDone]);`","correct":false},{"text":"`useEffect(() => { setDone(true); }, [done, setDone]);`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nfunction MyComponent(props) {\n  const [done, setDone] = useState(false);\n  return <h1>Done: {done}</h1>;\n}\n```"},{"question":". What value of button will allow you to pass the name of the person to be hugged?","options":[{"text":"`<button onClick={(name) => this.hug(name)>Hug Button</button>`","correct":true},{"text":"`<button onClick={this.hug(e, name)}>Hug Button</button>`","correct":false},{"text":"`<button onClick={(e) => hug(e, name)}>Hug Button</button>`","correct":false},{"text":"`<button onClick={(e) => this.hug(name, e)}>Hug Button</button>`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nclass Huggable extends React.Component {\n  hug(id) {\n    console.log(\"hugging \" + id);\n  }\n  render() {\n    let name = \"kitteh\";\n    let button = // Missing Code\n    return button;\n  }\n}\n```"},{"question":". Currently, `handleClick` is being called instead of passed as a reference. How do you fix this?","options":[{"text":"`<button onClick={this.handleClick.bind(handleClick)}>Click this</button>`","correct":false},{"text":"`<button onClick={handleClick()}>Click this</button>`","correct":false},{"text":"`<button onClick={this.handleClick}>Click this</button>`","correct":true},{"text":"`<button onclick={this.handleClick}>Click this</button>`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\n<button onClick={this.handleClick()}>Click this</button>\n```"},{"question":". Which answer best describes a function component?","options":[{"text":"A function component is the same as a class component.","correct":false},{"text":"A function component accepts a single props object and returns a React element.","correct":true},{"text":"A function component is the only way to create a component.","correct":false},{"text":"A function component is required to create a React component.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which library does the `fetch()` function come from?","options":[{"text":"FetchJS","correct":false},{"text":"ReactDOM","correct":false},{"text":"No library. `fetch()` is supported by most browsers.","correct":true},{"text":"React","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What will happen when this useEffect Hook is executed, assuming name is not already equal to John?","options":[{"text":"It will cause an error immediately.","correct":false},{"text":"It will execute the code inside the function, but only after waiting to ensure that no other component is accessing the name variable.","correct":false},{"text":"It will update the value of name once and not run again until name is changed from the outside.","correct":true},{"text":"It will cause an infinite loop.","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nuseEffect(() => {\n  setName('John');\n}, [name]);\n```"},{"question":". Which choice will not cause a React component to rerender?","options":[{"text":"if the component calls `this.setState(...)`","correct":false},{"text":"the value of one of the component's props changes","correct":false},{"text":"if the component calls `this.forceUpdate()`","correct":false},{"text":"one of the component's siblings rerenders","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You have created a new method in a class component called handleClick, but it is not working. Which code is missing?","options":[{"text":"`this.handleClick.bind(this);`","correct":false},{"text":"`props.bind(handleClick);`","correct":false},{"text":"`this.handleClick.bind();`","correct":false},{"text":"`this.handleClick = this.handleClick.bind(this);`","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nclass Button extends React.Component{\n  constructor(props) {\n    super(props);\n    // Missing line\n  }\n  handleClick() {...}\n}\n```"},{"question":". React does not render two sibling elements unless they are wrapped in a fragment. Below is one way to render a fragment. What is the shorthand for this?","options":[{"text":"A","correct":false},{"text":"B","correct":false},{"text":"C","correct":true},{"text":"D","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\n<Frag>\n  <h1>Our Staff</h1>\n  <p>Our staff is available 9-5 to answer your questions</p>\n</Frag>\n```"},{"question":". If you wanted to display the count state value in the component, what do you need to add to the curly braces in the `h1`?","options":[{"text":"this.state.count","correct":true},{"text":"count","correct":false},{"text":"state","correct":false},{"text":"state.count","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nclass Ticker extends React.component {\n  constructor(props) {\n    super(props);\n    this.state = { count: 0 };\n  }\n  render() {\n    return <h1>{}</h1>;\n  }\n}\n```"},{"question":". Per the following code, when is the Hello component displayed?","options":[{"text":"never","correct":false},{"text":"when `isLoggedIn` is true","correct":true},{"text":"when a user logs in","correct":false},{"text":"when the Hello function is called","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst greeting = isLoggedIn ? <Hello /> : null;\n```"},{"question":". In the following code block, what type is orderNumber?","options":[{"text":"string","correct":true},{"text":"boolean","correct":false},{"text":"object","correct":false},{"text":"number","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nReactDOM.render(<Message orderNumber=\"16\" />, document.getElementById('root'));\n```"},{"question":". You have added a style property to the `h1` but there is an unexpected token error when it runs. How do you fix this?","options":[{"text":"`const element = <h1 style=\"backgroundColor: \"blue\"\"}>Hi</h1>;`","correct":false},{"text":"`const element = <h1 style={{backgroundColor: \"blue\"}}>Hi</h1>;`","correct":true},{"text":"`const element = <h1 style={blue}>Hi</h1>;`","correct":false},{"text":"`const element = <h1 style=\"blue\">Hi</h1>;`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst element = <h1 style={ backgroundColor: \"blue\" }>Hi</h1>;\n```"},{"question":". Which function is used to update state variables in a React class component?","options":[{"text":"`replaceState`","correct":false},{"text":"`refreshState`","correct":false},{"text":"`updateState`","correct":false},{"text":"`setState`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Consider the following component. What is the default color for the star?","options":[{"text":"black","correct":false},{"text":"red","correct":false},{"text":"grey","correct":true},{"text":"white","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst Star = ({ selected = false }) => <Icon color={selected ? 'red' : 'grey'} />;\n```"},{"question":". Which answer best describes a function component?(Not sure answer)","options":[{"text":"`A function component is the same as a class component.`","correct":false},{"text":"`A function component accepts a single props object and returns a React element.`","correct":true},{"text":"`A function component is the only way to create a component.`","correct":false},{"text":"`A function component is required to create a React component.`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":".Which library does the fetch() function come from?","options":[{"text":"`FetchJS`","correct":false},{"text":"`ReactDOM`","correct":false},{"text":"`No library. fetch() is supported by most browsers.`","correct":true},{"text":"`React`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":".What is the difference between the click behaviors of these two buttons(assuming that this.handleClick is bound correctly)","options":[{"text":"`Button A will not have access to the event object on click of the button`","correct":false},{"text":"`Button A will not fire the handler this.handleClick successfully`","correct":false},{"text":"`There is no difference`","correct":false},{"text":"`Button B will not fire the handler this.handleClick successfully`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\n  A. <button onClick=this.handleClick>Click Me</button>\n  B. <button onClick={event => this.handleClick(event)}>Click Me</button>\n```"},{"question":".What will happen when this useEffect Hook is executed, assuming name is not already equal to John?","options":[{"text":"`It will cause an error immediately.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It will execute the code inside the function, but only after waiting to ensure that no other component is accessing the name variable.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It will update the value of name once and not run again until name is changed from the outside.`","correct":true},{"text":"`It will cause an infinite loop.`","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nuseEffect(() => {\n  setName('John');\n}, [name]);\n```"},{"question":". How would you add to this code, from React Router, to display a component called About?","options":[],"illustrator":"```javascript\n<Route path=\"/:id\" />\n```\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n          (\n            <Route path=\"/:id\">\n              {' '}\n              <About />\n            </Route>\n          )```\n                      ````\n                  `````;\n          ``````;\n          ```````\n      ````````\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n          (<Route path=\"/tid\" about={Component} />)```\n                      ````\n                  `````;\n          ``````;\n          ```````\n      ````````\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n          (<Route path=\"/:id\" route={About} />)```\n                      ````\n                  `````;\n          ``````;\n          ```````\n      ````````\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n          )```\n                      ````\n                  `````;\n          ``````;\n          ```````\n      ````````"},{"question":". Which class-based component is equivalent to this function component?","options":[],"illustrator":"```javascript\nconst Greeting ({ name }) > <h1>Hello {name}!</h1>;\n```\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n          class Greeting extends React.Component {\n            constructor() {\n              return <h1>Hello (this.props.name)!</h1>;\n            }\n          }\n          ```\n                      ````\n                  `````;\n          ``````;\n          ```````\n      ````````\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n                          ```\n                      ````\n                  `````\n              ``````\n          ```````\n      ````````\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n                             class Greeting extends React.Component { return <h1>Hello (this.props.name) 1</h1>; }\n                          ```\n                      ````\n                  `````\n              ``````\n          ```````\n      ````````\n- [ ] ````````javascript\n                          ```\n                      ````\n                  `````\n              ``````\n          ```````\n      ````````"},{"question":". Give the code below, what does the second argument that is sent to the render function describe?","options":[{"text":"where the React element should be added to the DOM","correct":true},{"text":"where to call the function","correct":false},{"text":"where the root component is","correct":false},{"text":"where to create a new JavaScript file","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nReactDOM.render(\n  <h1>Hi<h1>,\n    document.getElementById('root')\n)\n```"},{"question":". Why should you use React Router's Link component instead of a basic `<a>` tag in React?","options":[{"text":"The link component allows the user to use the browser's `Back` button.","correct":false},{"text":"There is no difference--the `Link` component is just another name for the `<a>` tag.","correct":false},{"text":"The `<a>` tag will cause an error when used in React.","correct":false},{"text":"The `<a>` tag triggers a full page reload, while the `Link` component does not.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the first argument, `x`, that is sent to the `createElement` function?","options":[{"text":"the element that should be created","correct":true},{"text":"the order in which this element should be placed on the page","correct":false},{"text":"the properties of the element","correct":false},{"text":"data that should be displayed in the element","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nReact.createElement(x, y, z);\n```"},{"question":". Which class-based lifecycle method would be called at the same time as this effect Hook?","options":[{"text":"componentWillUnmount","correct":false},{"text":"componentDidMount","correct":true},{"text":"render","correct":false},{"text":"componentDidUpdate","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nuseEffect(() => {\n  // do things\n}, []);\n```"},{"question":". Given the code below, what does the second argument that is sent to the render function describe?","options":[{"text":"where the React element should be added to the DOM","correct":true},{"text":"where to call the function","correct":false},{"text":"where the root component is","correct":false},{"text":"where to create a new JavaScript file","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```javascript\nReactDOM.render(\n  <h1>Hi</h1>\n  document.getElementById('root')\n);\n```"},{"question":". What is the first argument, x, that is sent to the `createElement` function?","options":[{"text":"the element that should be created","correct":true},{"text":"the order in which this element should be placed on the page","correct":false},{"text":"the properties of the element","correct":false},{"text":"data that should be displayed in the element.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""}]